(Stuart:)staying at your mom's
through all this.
I-I couldn't have done it
otherwise.
(Howard:)I appreciate that,
and I'm glad you were able to...
(Howard:)Is that my mother's furniture?
(Stuart:)Yeah, she said
I could use it.
(Stuart:)Doesn't it look
great?
(Howard:)Not as great as it looks in
the den where it belongs.
(Bernadette:)Howie.
(Howard:)Why don't you just clean out
the whole room?
(Howard:)Take the string art clown
I made her in third grade
(Howard:)and the ribbon I got
in swim class
(Howard:)for putting my face
in the water.
(Stuart:)What is your problem?
(Stuart:)She said it was okay.
(Howard:)Well, I'm her son,
and I say it's not okay.
(Stuart:)Some son-- looks like you spent
ten minutes on that clown art.
(Howard:)Well, maybe I should've gone
to a fancy art school like you.
(Howard:)Then I could run
a failed comic shop
(Howard:)and mooch off
some guy's mother.
(Bernadette:)Why don't we leave
so you can cool off?
(Stuart:)I think that's
a good idea.
(Stuart:)Take him out
of my store.
Your store?!
(Howard:)My mother gave you
the money to reopen.
(Howard:)I'm not going anywhere.
(Leonard:)Why don't we go get
the food for the party.
(Barry:)Thank you.
(Raj:)Smart-- looks like
we're being helpful.